Ice Sculpture Christmas is a romance, tv movie film directed by David Mackay.
After starting her first job at a country club restaurant, Callie’s passions for cooking and ice sculpting are met with romance and Christmas
spirit when a childhood friend enters her into the club’s annual Christmas ice sculpting competition without her knowledge.
Callie Shaw, played by Rachel Boston.
David Manning, played by David Alpay.
Chef Gloria, played by Brenda Strong.
Frank Shaw, played by Paul McGillion.
Brooke, played by Aliyah O'Brien.
Ellis Manning, played by Mark Brandon.
Dylan Kingwell (born July 6, 2004) is a Canadian actor.
He is known for playing the roles of Duncan and Quigley Quagmire in the Netflix television series A Series of
Unfortunate Events and, since 2022, has starred as Sam Price in the BYUtv series Ruby and the Well.
He has also had notable recurring roles as Steve Murphy in the ABC drama series The
Good Doctor and as the teenaged Clark Kent in Superman & Lois for the CW.
He portrayed Arthur Henderson in Hallmark's Campfire Kiss.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship,
competition, childhood friends, country club, ice sculpture.
The tone is emotional.